I've been living here for twenty-seven days
inside a Chevette.
The problem is that the money is coming in and
Chevette is listening
I had to cancel the gym.
let's say I had some technical problems
in life you have to learn.
if you don't have a dog,
starts hunting with cat.
It's been a few days since my back pain returned.
I took the bench here
to make a space to transport a dog
and it didn't work.
now I'm out of business,
without a bench and without a bed.
and then chevas went wrong.
I promised truffle to a customer,
I said I was going to stop by.
the chevas gave trouble.
now i'm here at the barbershop,
I will deliver flyer,
but OR do you accept this situation
OR do you do something different to change it.
Man,
won't believe the message I got.
big deal,
I got an invitation from the Cocoa Show,
brother,
I got an invitation from the Cocoa Show.
I received an invitation from the Cocoa Show
here huh?
our bro,
he goes making 1 funnel.
bro,
you have to be smaller,
do you have more wood like this?
I don't.